# Jaturong Duangchaiyusuk, Team Lead & Senior Full Stack Developer

Email: jaturong.duang@gmail.com Mobile: (+66) 86 906 8319

Date of Birth: 6 Feb 1990 Nationality: Thai Gender: Male

Github: <a href="https://github.com/srankmeng">https://github.com/srankmeng</a>
Website: <a href="https://srankmeng.github.io/personal-web">https://srankmeng.github.io/personal-web</a>

# Summary / Profile:

I have experience with 10+ years of Web development. For technical skills such as frontend, backend, automated testing, devOps, and AWS services (EC2, ECS, S3, Lambda, etc.). I used to use the Agile process in my projects which have planning, backlog refinement, daily stand up, and retrospective. And I can use tools that are related to my tasks. In addition, I supported the team like a review the code, coaching team members, and finding solutions when having problems delivering tasks on time for team success.

#### **Employment History:**

Feb 2023 - Present

Full Stack Developer Consultant, Siam Chamnankit Bangkok, Thailand

- Collaborated with clients to understand business requirements, and conducted needs assessments
- Creating a pipeline for automated testing and delivery projects
- Provided ongoing technical support, troubleshooting, and enhancements for existing applications

May 2021 - Jul 2022

Team Lead Developer, Redlamp Co., Ltd.

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team to clarify the requirement
- Planning & clearing issue blocks for delivering the project on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Nest js for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Use Cypress for E2E automate part
- The delivery website which client site and back-office site

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021

#### Team Lead Developer, SCG

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team to clarify the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery of projects on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Flask for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Delivery website <a href="https://www.scg-id.com">https://www.scg-id.com</a> that includes back-office site

Jan 2017 - Dec 2019

## Frontend Team Lead & Senior Developer, Lqid 360 Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- · Planning & resource management for the delivery of projects on time
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use React, Redux for frontend web development
- Motivation team members and making teamwork
- Use jest for unit test
- Discussing with backend team for design response api
- Delivery KYC's back-office
- Delivery chat system use in back-office with WebRTC technology
- Delivery monitoring system display with chart

May 2012 - Dec 2016

# Frontend Developer

Bangkok, Thailand

- Created HTML & CSS related to designs
- Use jquery to manage data on the frontend side
- Use Angularis v1 to manage data on the frontend side
- Integrate API and display data
- Delivery BigC check QC back-office
- Delivery E-commerce web
- Support team & issues

### **Educations:**

May 2008 - Apr 2012

Computer Engineering Bachelor's Degree Bangkok, Thailand King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang (KMITL)

Skills:

Javascript Liff Skillful Expert Vue, Nuxt Expert Docker Experienced **AWS** React, Redux Experienced Experienced Github Action React Native Skillful Skillful Html & CSS Skillful Expert Azure Terraform Jquery Expert Experienced Bootstrap MongoDB Skillful Expert Nest js, Node js PostgresSQL & MySQL Experienced Experienced **Typescript** Elastic search Experienced Experienced Python Skillful Odoo Skillful

	Flutter Go Git	Experienced Skillful Expert	Firebase Cypress Agile	Skillful Skillful Experienced
Languages:	Thai	Native	English	good command

**Hobbies:** Cinema, Japanese manga, Watching football, Beer